Artifical Abandonment
人工的な放棄
Original song by JonKaGor
オリジナル曲：JonKaGor
If I was really a treasure to you,
もし私があなたにとって本当に宝物だったのなら、
I'm deserted by the one I trusted the most
私が最も信頼していた人に見捨てられてしまう
Knowing you'll do the same as everyone,
あなたも皆と同じことをするだろうとわかっていれば、
I'll be removed, and you will be gone.
私は連れ去られ、あなたもいなくなるでしょう。
"Please, don't ever try to leave me behind."
「お願い、絶対に私を置いて行かないでください。」
But, clearly I know from the start
でも、明らかに最初からそれが嘘だとわかっています
It's a lie.
それは嘘です。
Seeing you laugh with the figures you love
あなたが愛するフィギュアたちと笑っているのを見ると、
To all you call "precious"
あなたが「大切」と呼ぶすべての人に「
"Replace me now."
今すぐ私を代えてください」
In this world, we keep lusting for something new,
この世界では、私たちは何か新しいものを欲しがり続けますが、
One day, slowly all will forget with it too.
ある日、ゆっくりと、私たちもそれを忘れてしまいます。
Finally, we'll crave for abandonment
最後に、僕たちは見捨てられることを切望し
then, end up discarding ourselves
、結局は自分自身を捨ててしまう。
(Instrumental break)
（インストゥルメンタル ブレイク）
If I was really a treasure to you,
もし僕が君にとって本当に宝物だったのなら、
I'm deserted by the one I trusted the most
僕が最も信頼していた人に見捨てられてしまう。僕が君を捨てた
Scared that you'll do the same as everyone
みんなと同じことを君もしてしまうのではないかと怖い。
I have left you before it is done
それが終わる前に。
"Please, don't ever try to leave me behind."
「お願い、僕を置き去りにしないで。」
But, clearly I know from the start
でも、明らかに最初からそれが嘘だとわかっています
It's a lie.
それは嘘です。
That time you smiled next to me, who you loved
愛した私の隣で微笑んだあの時、
As you called me, "precious",
あなたは私を「大切」と呼び、
"Don't leave me now."
「もう離さないで」と言った。
And somehow, your hand is now out of my reach
そしてどういうわけか、あなたの手は今私の手の届かないところにあります。
My voice can be heard, but there's no way to speak
私の声は聞こえますが、話す方法はありません。
I lied that seeing your smile from afar
遠くからあなたの笑顔を見るだけで、
Will always be enough for me
私には十分であると嘘をつきました。
And though,
そして、
in this world we keep lusting for something new
この世界で私たちは何か新しいものを欲しがり続けていますが、
One day, slowly all will forget with it too.
ある日、ゆっくりとすべても忘れてしまいます。
In the end, who craved for abandonment
結局、見捨てられることを渇望していたのは
Was this creature I call "myself"
「自分」と呼ぶこの生き物だった